我和我的兄弟姊妹是历史上
最早的吸血鬼
KLAUS: My siblings and I
are the first vampires in all of history.
是真祖家族
The Originals.
三百年前，我们帮助建立了纽奥良
Three hundred years ago,
we helped build New Orleans.
现在我们回来
发现这座城市有了新的王
Now we have returned
to find the city has a new king,
在一个强大女孩的帮助下统治着城市
one who rules with the aid
of a powerful girl.
他们俘掳了我哥哥以利亚
They have taken possession
of my brother Elijah.
女巫们很想要那个女孩
A coven of witches
want this girl for themselves.
她们力图得到我的帮助
The seek to enlist my help,
利用我未出生的孩子做筹码
using my unborn child
as leverage,
但我怀疑她们别有用心
though I suspect they have
ulterior motives.
所以我制定了自己的计划
So, I've made a plan
of my own.
我将救出我哥哥
并将这座城市重新收回我家族手中
I will free my brother and
reclaim the city for our family.
那时我将成为王
Then I will be king.
在我的一生当中
KLAUS:
Over the course of my life,
我遇到的人里
I've encountered no shortage
of those who would presume
不乏擅自判定善恶的
to speak of good and evil.
这样的说法根本毫无意义
Such terms mean nothing.
人们会做对自己最有利的事
People do what is
in their best interest,
不顾会因此受伤的人
regardless of who gets hurt.
得到自己想要的，满足欲望
Is it evil to take
what one wants,
即使这么做会让他人蒙受痛苦
to satisfy hunger
even if doing so
这样邪恶吗？
will cause another's suffering?
人们所说的邪恶
What some would call evil
我认为是对残酷不公的世界
I believe to be
an appropriate response
的合理反应
to a harsh and unfair world.
无意冒犯，但我不确定我知道
No offense,
but I'm not sure I follow
你为何邀我来这里
why you've
invited me here.
因为我喜欢你的陪伴
Because I enjoy your company,
我感觉你能够理解
and I sense you have
the capacity
像我这样复杂的人
for understanding
someone of my complexity.
你知道我回纽奥良
You see, I returned
to New Orleans
是为了调查一个针对我的威胁
to investigate a threat
posed against me.
结果却发现有个年轻女人
What I found was
a young woman,
怀孕了，需要保护
pregnant,
in need of protection.
我哥哥，总是做好事的那个
My brother,
always the do-gooder,
试图操控我帮助她
tried to manipulate me
into helping her.
他觉得这也许能让我得到救赎
He thought it might redeem me.
问题是，我后来得知
Trouble is,
I've since learned
还有个年轻女人
确切说是女孩
of another young women,
a girl really,
一个拥有巨大潜力的女孩
one with vast potential,
被一个暴君所囚禁
held in captivity by a tyrant.
我想要帮助这两个女人
I want to help both of these women.
保护一个，解救另一个
Protect one and free the other.
所以告诉我，卡蜜
So tell me, Cami.
你觉得这邪恶吗？
Does that sound evil to you?
我不觉得邪恶是绝对的
I don't believe in
evil as a diagnosis.
我觉得你的人际关系非常不稳定
I think you have unstable
personal relationships,
还有受压力影响的妄想症
stress-related paranoia,
长期的愤怒管理问题，害怕被抛弃
chronic anger issues,
fear of abandonment.
我觉得你和专业人士聊聊也许会有帮助
I think you could benefit from
talking to someone professionally.
我觉得我更喜欢和你聊
I think I prefer to talk to you.
所以我打算提供一份工作给你
So I'm going to offer you a job
做我的速记员
as my stenographer.
好啊，要写什么？
Okay.
What are we writing?
当然是我的回忆录
My memoirs of course.
我的故事应该被人所知
Someone should
know my story,
这也会让我们有时间讨论
and it will give us time
to discuss
其他有趣的话题
other riveting subjects,
比如你师气的追求者马赛尔
Iike your handsome suitor Marcel.
抱歉，我的私生活…
Excuse me.
My private life is--
你的私生活，事实证明
Your private life is,
as it turns out,
对我的计划至关重要
essential to my plans.
马赛尔想要得到你
You see, Marcel wants you,
正因如此，他会信任你
and because of that,
he will trust you,
这点对我很有利
which serves me.
最重要的是，法语区
The thing is
the French Quarter
的战争一触即发
is on the verge of war.
一方是我
On the one side, there's me,
另一方是马赛尔
and on the other, Marcel,
还有那个法力无边的女巫
以及一支吸血鬼部队
along with a very powerful witch
and an army of vampires.
什么？
What?
你害怕了
You're frightened.
别害怕
Don't be.
我不害怕了
I'm not scared anymore.
太神奇了，你是怎么做到…
That's amazing.
How did you--
这叫魅惑
It's called compulsion.
这算是吸血鬼的小手段
It's a neat bit of vampire trickery.
我会全都告诉你的
I'll tell you all about it,
但首先，我们来多聊聊马赛尔吧
but first, let's talk
a little more about Marcel.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：纽奥良女孩
这泥蛋复原能力还真强
MARCEL: Sucker's resilient.
他就像穿着西装的蟑螂
He's like a cockroach
in a suit.
没关系
该把老家伙以利亚还给克劳斯了
Doesn't matter. Time to give
old Elijah back to Klaus anyway.
你要我弄清楚怎样才能杀死真祖
主演：约瑟夫摩根
You asked me to figure out
how to kill the Originals.
我还没弄清楚呢
I'm not done.
银匕首能够伤害他们，但仅此而已
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
Silver dagger hurts them,
but that's it.
黛维娜，我们讨论过了
Davina, we've been through this.
克劳斯救了我的命，我欠他一个人情
主演：克莱儿荷特
Klaus saved my life.
I owe him one.
既然他想要回他哥哥…
Since he wants his brother back--
今晚是一年一度的多芬街音乐节
Tonight's the annual
Dauphine Street Music Festival.
我想去
I want to go.
求求你
Please.
你之所以要待在这里
主演：菲比托金
The whole point of you
being up here
就是为了永远不会在外面被人发现
is so you're never spotted out there.
你知道谁在多芬街讨生活
You know who works smack in
the middle of Dauphine street.
苏菲德弗罗
Sophie Deveraux,
最难搞的女巫
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
pain-in-the-ass witch,
你也知道如果女巫们找到你
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
and you know what the witches
will do to you
会对你做些什么
if they find you.
但你控制着这些女巫
But you control the witches.
让她走开就是了
Make her go away.
马赛尔，就一晚
Marcel, it's one night.
我说了不行
I said no.
我对你言听计从
I do anything you say,
但有时我觉得你忘记我的能耐了
but sometimes,
I think you forget what I'm capable of.
你知道我能让一个人的血沸腾吗？
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
Did you know I can make
someone's blood boil?
我只要集中精神
All I have to do is focus.
主演：莉雅派普斯
(HlSSlNG, FlzzLlNG)
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
好吧，我们各让一步，好吗？
Fine.
We compromise, all right?
你一个人出去太危险了
You going out, alone,
too dangerous,
但我会把你介绍给一位
也要去那的朋友
but I'll introduce you to a friend
of mine that's gonna be there.
好吗？很不错的小姐
All right?
Nice lady.
你们俩会很合得来的
You two are really gonna hit it off.
你好，卡蜜
Hello, Cami.
为什么你一接近我
How is it that when
you come up to me now
周围又没人的时候
and no one else is around
我突然就想起来你刚告诉过我
I suddenly remember
that you just told me
你是个吸血鬼，你对我使用精神控制
you're a vampire and
you're mind-controlling me.
而你一离开，我就会只想着
And then you leave,
and I go back to thinking
你是个性感的男人
you're just some hot guy
口音很迷人，而且挥金如土
with a cute accent and money to burn
写什么乱七八糟的回忆录？
on your sprawling memoir?
魅惑就是这样，亲爱的
制片：兰斯安德森
Well, that's how
compulsion works, love.
是啊，但这是怎么回事？
Yeah, but what's happening?
这是催眠吗？我的神经元被关闭了吗？
Is it hypnosis, are my neurons
being shut down somehow?
你总是个好奇的学者
You're always the curious scholar.
我们来聊聊马赛尔吧
Let's talk about Marcel.
你说你有点消息要告诉我
You said you have
a little information for me.
他今晚要带一个人去音乐节
He's bringing someone
to the music festival tonight,
他指导的一个女孩
a girl he's mentoring.
显然她正在经历艰难的时刻
Apparently she's going
through a hard time,
反抗权威、愤怒管理问题
rebelling against authority,
anger issues,
之类的
that sort of thing.
我猜因为我有心理学学位
I guess with my
psych degree
他觉得我能帮助她步入正途
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
he figured I could set her straight,
但我拒绝了
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
but I said no.
我要坚持请你
I'm gonna go ahead
and insist
改变回答，答应他
you change
your answer to yes.
你要强迫我这么做，是吗？
You're gonna force me
to do this, aren't you?
那干嘛还这么客气呢？
Why even bother with politeness?
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
我喜欢你的思考方式
I like the way your mind works.
要是换个情况
Under different circumstances,
我想我们也许会成为朋友
I think we might be friends.
然而
However,
我不能错过
编剧：蜜雪儿佩洛戴斯，麦克纳度奇
I don't have the luxury
今晚的绝佳机会
of passing up
tonight's opportunity.
除了是马赛尔的强大秘密武器之外
导演：杰西瓦恩
You see, in addition to being Marcel's
rather potent secret weapon,
这个女孩黛维娜还俘掳着我哥哥
this girl Davina
is holding my brother captive.
换句话说
In other words,
这个女孩需要你的帮助
the girl needs your help.
打电话给马赛尔
Call Marcel,
告诉他你很乐意帮忙
tell him you'll be happy to oblige.
我说过了，爱格妮丝，我感觉很好
I told you, Agnes,
I feel great.
你错过了健康检查
You are overdue for a checkup.
那我要怎么做
匆匆跑进法语区做个快速超音波吗？
What am I gonna do, pop into
the Quarter for a quick ultrasound?
一个在女巫陪同下的狼人孕妇？
A pregnant werewolf
escorted by a witch?
绝对没什么可看的
Nothing to see here.
有许多女人非常渴望怀上孩子
A lot of women
would kill to have a child.
我觉得很奇怪
你都没好好照顾你的孩子
Strikes me as odd that
you're not taking better care of yours.
我认识一个在河口偏僻地方的医生
I know a doctor out in the bayou,
off the beaten path.
我擅自做主替你预约了
Now, I took the liberty
of making an appointment
今晚下班后的时间，只有我们
for you tonight.
After hours, just us.
吸血鬼不会得到消息的
Vampires will never
get word of it.
好，就这样吧
Okay. Fine.
就河口的小儿科医生了
Bayou baby doctor it is.
拜托，妹妹
告诉我你不会还在
Please, sister,
tell me you're not still at it
网上搜寻吧
with the lnternet search.
不过这到底要怎么搜
How does one begin anyway,
输入“无名阁楼”吗？
just type in "anonymous attic"?
总得有人找到以利亚
Someone has to find Elijah,
即使我得搜遍纽奥良每一个该死的阁楼
even if I have to search
every bloody attic in New Orleans.
这就像是在
Like looking for a needle
大海捞针啊
in a rather large pile of needles.
我记得马赛尔带我去的那个阁楼的细节
I remember details about
the attic Marcel took me to.
以利亚棺材后面的窗户上
There were shutters
on the windows
有百叶窗
behind Elijah's coffin.
这样范围就缩小很多了
Well, that should
narrow it down immensely.
我个人而言，比起麻木的脑力劳动
Myself, I prefer actual strategy
更喜欢实际的策略
as opposed to mind-numbing labor.
马赛尔迟迟不归还我们的哥哥
Marcel's delay
in returning our brother
让我怀疑他不再掌控着整个局面
makes me suspect he's no longer
in charge of the situation.
如果黛维娜对马赛尔的忠诚紧张起来
If Davina's loyalty to Marcel is strained,
也许这个年轻女巫将会愿意
perhaps the young witch
will be open to
接受新的盟友
discussing a new alliance.
一如既往，你对权力的争夺比救回
As usual, your power grabs
are more important
你哥哥还要重要
than rescuing your brother.
我倒觉得这是一石二鸟之计
I prefer to think of it as killing
two birds with one stone.
抢走马赛尔的秘密武器
Rob Marcel of his secret weapon...
把我们的哥哥带回家
...bring our brother home.
嘿，迪亚哥
Hey, Diego.
好吧，有没有能得到
Right. So... any way to fast track
日光戒指的捷径呢？
the whole getting a daylight ring thing?
当你被邀请进入亲信圈的时候
就能得到日光戒指
You get a daylight right when you
get invited to the inner circle.
你嘛，大概永远都不可能了
For you, it may never happen.
但还是有机会的，对吧？
Yeah, but there's an opening, right?
既然提艾里已经…你懂的
I mean, now that Thierry's, like,
you know--
不许再提提艾里，明白吗？
You shut up about Thierry,
all right?
他不该得到这样的下场
He didn't deserve what he got.
马赛尔只是在向克劳斯炫耀
Marcel was just showing off for Klaus.
真等不及让这个老不死的滚出这里
(DOOR OPENS)
Can't wait till his
ancient ass is out of here.
你和我想的一样
You and me both.
注意点，各位
这里来了一位
Look alive, boys.
We got ourselves
高贵的吸血鬼真祖
one high-class Original vampire.
小嘴真甜
A real charmer.
要是我告诉你我能帮你解决
What if I told you that
I could help you out
克劳斯的问题
with your Klaus problem in exchange
换取一点点小八卦怎么样？
for the tiniest bit of gossip?
比如？
Like what?
你应该听说过我和马赛尔
You might have heard the rumors
that Marcel and l
过去的风流韵事
were quite the item back in the day.
他似乎移情别恋了
He seems to have moved on,
而我想知道是和谁
and I would like to know with whom.
你看到他和那个酒保了
You've seen him with the bartender.
他调情的那个普通女孩吗？
What, that plain Jane
that he carries on with?
只有瞎了眼的男人才会选她而不选我
Well, only a blind man
would choose her over me.
他的后宫里一定还有另一个女孩
There must be another girl in his harem.
听着，我只想要一个真正的结束
Look. I just need the
tiniest bit of closure,
然后我就可以离开纽奥良
and then I can leave
New Orleans,
我会保证带着克劳斯一起走
and I'll be sure to take Klaus with me,
这样的话，承认吧
这会让你的生活轻松许多
which, let's face it,
would make your life a whole lot easier.
听着，马赛尔事情非常多
Look.
Marcel's got a full plate.
如果他有在跟其他女人约会
If he's seeing some other honey,
她就一定在法语区
she's somewhere in the Quarter.
可能就在附近
She's probably close by.
小姐，我只知道这些
And that, my lady, is all I got.
（第22届多芬街音乐节）
今晚可是大活动，有许多人会喝酒
Big event tonight,
a lot of people drinking,
有许多眼睛看着
a lot of eyes watching.
我不想要有麻烦
I don't want any trouble,
也就是说不能有女巫
which means no witches.
去跟女巫们传个话
Send word through the Cauldron.
只要有女巫来，我们就杀掉
Any witches come here, we kill them.
说到这里，也不能有真祖
And while we're at it, no Originals.
我不喜欢蕾贝卡到处打探
I don't like how Rebekah's
been snooping around.
我邀请了卡蜜一起来
她还有她的一位朋友
I got my girl Cami coming,
her and a little friend of hers.
我希望随时有人盯着她们
I want eyes on them at all times.
只能盯着，明白吗？
Eyes only, all right?
我不希望有任何人靠近她们
I don't want anybody going
anywhere near either of them.
大家都有各自的岗位，所有人都警觉点
Everybody's got a post,
everybody keeps an eye out.
明白吗？
We cool?
这是你期待的吗？
So is it everything you hoped for?
是啊
Yeah!
那么我们该复习一下规矩了
So we should probably
go over the rules.
我不会和任何人说任何事
I won't talk to anyone about anything.
我不会说任何有关女巫或吸血鬼
I won't say anything
about witches or vampires
或真祖或你的事
or Originals or you.
但你说过你不会黏着我的
But you said you weren't gonna hover.
这是医生的办公室？
This is the doctor's office?
佩吉医生就住这么偏远
Dr. Paige is only this far out
因为马赛尔的手下一直恐吓她的病人
because Marcel's men kept
terrorizing her patients.
去吧，她又不会咬你
Go.
She won't bite.
让他们进去，告诉他们下手快点
Send them in now
and tell them to do it quickly.
见到你真好
It's good to see you.
我还担心在化妆舞会上的表现之后
I was worried you thought
I was some hot head
你会以为我是个性急的人呢
after that display
at the masquerade.
我们都有性急的时候
We all have
our hot-headed moments.
总之，在清理前，我没什么事可做了
Anyway, I'm almost done here
until cleanup,
所以我们两个女孩可以一起玩
so the two of us girls
can hang out
如果你需要去聊天或是什么的
if you need to go
schmooze or whatever.
你知道吗，他十分钟前就该离开这了
You know, he was supposed to stop
hovering, like, ten minutes ago.
你懂我说的话了吧，管不住了
You see what I mean?
Authority issues.
我去和市长聊聊
I'll go talk to the mayor.
他倒是知道要如何表现尊重
He actually knows
how to show some respect.
他叫什么名字？
So, what's his name?
拉小提琴的师哥
Hot guy with the fiddle.
提姆
Tim.
我就知道他会来
I knew he'd be here.
他总是在这样的场合演出
He always performs
at these kind of things.
你们俩认识多久了？
How long have you two
known each other?
十岁时就认识了
Since we were ten.
我不得不退学
I had to leave school,
我没有机会道别
and I didn't get to say good-bye,
我只希望今晚能和他说两句话
so I was just hoping
to talk to him tonight.
很好
That's it!
教堂关门了
Church is closed.
你想要我刺激，去鬼屋吧
You want your horror fix,
go take a ghost tour.
我不太喜欢鬼
I don't much care for ghosts.
不过我对百叶窗很着迷
I am, however,
fascinated by window shutters.
我一整天都在城里观赏百叶窗
I've been on a town tour
of them all day.
我注意到你阁楼的窗户上有百叶窗
I noticed the windows
of your attic have shutters.
你真的是对百叶窗感兴趣吗？
Are you really interested in shutters?
我向你保证这是我现在最着迷的东西
I can assure
it's my current life obsession.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
基兰神父，你呢？
Father Kieran, and you are?
小好奇小姐
Mildly curious.
这里发生了什么事？
What happened here?
圣安妮教堂曾是这一带的中心
St. Anne's used to be
the heart of the neighborhood.
自从那晚大屠杀之后
It's been abandoned
for a while now.
已经被废弃了一阵子了
Since the night of the massacre.
九名神学生被他们的一个同学杀死
Nine seminary students were killed
by one of their own.
不！
No!
你就站在血迹之上
You're standing on blood.
我没那么容易吐
I'm not squeamish.
阁楼在哪？
Where's the attic?
我刚才说了，教堂关门了
Like I said, the church is closed.
阁楼在哪？
Where is the attic?
圣器室后面的楼梯上面
Past the sacristy.
Up the stairs.
谢谢你
现在忘了我曾经来过这里
Thank you.
Now, forget I was here.
我就知道
I knew it.
搞什么鬼？
What the bloody hell?
蕾贝卡，请注意错辞
Rebekah, language, please.
以利亚
Elijah!
这些是什么？
What is all this?
你不记得了吗？
You don't remember?
你和我一起去了歌剧院
You and l
went to the opera house together.
那是克劳斯拔出你身上的匕首之后
It was your first foray
back into New Orleans society
你回到纽奥良的第一次劫掠
after Klaus removed the dagger from you.
这是只有你我共享的回忆
It's a memory that
only you and I share.
同时我还要让你知道
这不是黛维娜的另一个花招
Also I needed to know
it's not another of Davina's tricks.
你怎么会醒着？
Well, how are you even awake?
黛维娜拔出了匕首
Davina withdrew the dagger,
她不知道这么做哪怕只有一次
也会让它失去作用
unaware that doing so even once
would negate its power.
再过几小时，我就会复原了
In a few hours,
I shall be as good as new.
那让我回阁楼去
So, put me back into the attic,
我们就能想办法把你弄出去
and we can find a way
to get you out.
恐怕我还没有准备好
I'm afraid I'm not quite ready
离开呢，蕾贝卡
to leave yet, Rebekah.
这个女孩黛维娜，她很好奇
This girl, Davina, she's curious.
也很任性
Willful, too.
很快我就能和她聊聊了
Soon I shall be able
to speak to her,
也许还能提议某种形式的休战
perhaps even to propose
a truce of some kind.
如果我们能终止这场
So, if we can end this war
吸血鬼和女巫的战争
between the vampires and the witches,
我们就能清除
we'll be able to eliminate the threat
海莉和她孩子的威胁了
to Hayley and her baby.
也许那时，尼克劳斯和我们家族
Perhaps then Niklaus
and our entire family
终于能够享受安宁了
can finally know peace.
在此期间，我需要你照顾好海莉
In the meantime,
I need you to look after Hayley.
她现在是我们的家人了
She is our family now.
所以我需要她和她未出生的孩子
So, I need her
and her unborn child
能够受到我们的保护
to fall underneath our protection.
对我发誓，蕾贝卡
Swear to me, Rebekah.
我发誓
I swear.
你的宝宝的心率很正常
Your baby's heart rate is perfect.
我就知道，她和她妈妈一样坚强
I knew it.
She's a tough one like her mom.
那是很特别的胎记啊
That's a unique birthmark.
我们差不多可以了吧？
We're pretty much done here, right?
（蕾贝卡：你在哪？）
你的血压有点高
Your blood pressure's a bit high.
我帮你准备了一点药
I've got something for it.
（在河口诊所看医生）
那个…其实我不太喜欢吃药
Ah, you know,
I'm actually not that good with pills.
说实话，我也是
Well, me neither, truth be told.
你好，提姆
KLAUS: Hello, Tim.
我相信你和我都认识一个人
I believe you and l
share an acquaintance.
做个好孩子，帮我传话给她
Be a good lad and help me
send her a message.
他不可能走远的
Well, he couldn't have gone far.
他一分钟前才离开舞台
He just got offstage a minute ago.
没关系，反正这是个愚蠢的主意
It doesn't matter.
This was a stupid idea anyway.
不，不是的，黛维娜…
No, it wasn't.
Davina.
算了吧
Just forget it.
告诉她这是一个乐手给的
Tell her this is
from one of the musicians.
她会想离开
She'll want to leave,
她要带她从后门溜走
and you're going to help her
slip out the back exit
这样马赛尔就看不到了
so Marcel doesn't see.
不管你做什么
Whatever you do,
不要让她离开你的视线
don't let her out of your sight.
等一下，黛维娜
Wait, Davina!
我做不到
I can't do this.
你好
Hey.
提姆，我收到你的纸条了
Tim, I got your note.
我收到你的简讯了
I got your text message.
谢谢你来这里见我
Thanks for meeting me here.
能见到你真是太好了
It's so amazing to see you.
真不敢相信我现在居然站在这里
I can't even believe
I'm standing here right now.
我…
I just....
哇
Wow!
你去哪了？
So where have you been,
为什么想在这里见面？
and why did you want to meet here?
这里好阴森
It's so creepy,
发生过很多可怕的事
all the terrible stuff
that happened.
我也说不清，我还蛮喜欢这里的
I don't know.
I kind of like it.
这里很安静
You know, it's quiet.
一个地方不能因为发生了一件糟糕的事
I mean, the place can't
be bad for all time
就一直糟糕下去，对吧？
just because one bad thing
happened, right?
等等，不是，还是从头说起吧
Wait. No. All right.
Back up.
那天你突然就不来学校了
To where one day,
you just stop coming to school,
从此你就像蒸发了一样
and then it's like you just vanished.
是因为突发情况
我得去处理一些事情
There was an emergency,
and I needed to take care
of some things.
那你没事吧？
Are you okay?
你看起来没事
I mean, you look okay.
事实上，你看起来非常好
You look great, actually.
那你打算回学校吗？
So are you coming back to school?
不回去了
No.
但我要你知道，即便我离开了
But I need you to know
that even though I was away...
我依然想念你
...I miss you.
我想念能在学校看见你的日子
I miss seeing you at school
想念看你拉小提琴的日子
and seeing you play your violin.
其实
Well....
这地方音响效果还不错
This place does have good acoustics.
这孩子很有天赋
The boy has a gift.
要拉出这种感觉是魅惑不来的
You can't compel someone
to play like that.
我知道你是干什么的
I know what you are.
虽然我觉得很疯狂，但至少能说得通
It's crazy to me,
but at least it makes sense,
但这场杀戮
完全是残忍而没有意义的
but this massacre
was just a pointless, brutal thing.
你一生中，有听说过
In all your life,
have you ever heard
这样的事吗
of anything like that,
一个好人，一个有理想的牧师
a good man,
an aspiring priest,
没有缘由地掀起一场杀戮
just goes on a killing spree
out of nowhere.
我一生中见太多了
I've seen quite a lot in my time.
这个世界非常可怕
The world is a rather awful place.
最好得去适应它的规则
Best to meet it on its own terms.
不，这个世界并不可怕
No.
The world isn't awful.
人也不可怕
People are not awful.
他们是向善的
They want to be good.
是一些事让他们变坏
Something makes them bad.
把他们击倒
Something breaks them down,
让他们突然崩溃
makes them snap.
总会有迹象
There are always signs,
一个人精神崩溃之前一定有征兆
symptoms before someone
has a psychotic break.
但这凶手完全没有出现任何征兆
The guy who did this had none of them.
他不酗酒，不吸毒
He didn't drink,
he didn't do drugs.
你对这件事很了解啊
You're well-informed on the matter.
你认识他，是吗？
You knew him, didn't you?
他叫西恩
His name was Sean.
是我哥哥
He was my brother.
实际上是我的双胞胎哥哥
My twin actually.
我无法入眠
I can't sleep.
不停地梦见发生的一切
I dream about what happened...
我恨这种感觉
...and I hate it.
我恨自己不能帮他
I hate that I couldn't help him.
我们都要独自面对自己内心的恶魔
We all must stand alone
against our demons.
要是有一天这些恶魔
也在我心中滋生呢？
What if someday his demons
become mine too?
我有些事
I have some business
需要去处理
I should attend to
在我去之前
but before I do...
你该走了
You should go.
去欣赏音乐，别再想这些
Enjoy the music,
put this out of your mind.
马赛尔
Marcel.
基兰神父，欢迎回来
Father Kieran, welcome back.
我没想到你会回来
I wasn't sure when
you'd be coming home.
看得出来
I can tell,
看看我教堂阁楼里
发生了什么事就知道了
judging by what's going on
in my church attic.
我觉得你不会介意的
I didn't think you'd mind.
上帝为证，我帮过你一两个小忙
Lord knows,
I'd done you a favor or two.
我猜你已经知道真祖回来了
I take it you know
the Originals have returned.
那个妹妹蕾贝卡，我刚才看到她
The sister Rebekah,
I saw her earlier,
在教堂四处窥探，打听阁楼的事
snooping around the church,
asking about the attic.
她不知道我体内有马鞭草
She doesn't know I take vervain.
你有问题要处理了
You got a problem on your hands.
我对你和你教堂的哀悼方式
No disrespect for
the grieving process,
并无不敬之意
for you and your church,
但我想知道，你是来帮我的
but just so I know,
are you here to help,
还是专程来批评我的？
or are you just gonna drop in
with criticism?
永远记住，马赛尔
Never forget, Marcel,
你能在这个城市安身都是
that you live
in this city by the grace
拜那些知道你秘密
of those that know your secret
并容忍你的人们所赐
and tolerate you.
这个城市之所以繁荣是因为我
And this city thrives
because of me
和我的手下
and my people.
如果哪天你忘记这点了
Anytime you need a reminder of that,
让我来提醒你
just let me know.
马赛尔，迪亚哥说他跟丢了那两个女孩
Marcel, Diego said
he lost eyes on the girls.
回头接着聊
To be continued.
你们俩真的是太可爱了
You two are absolutely adorable.
我真的很感动，真的
It warms my heart,
it really does,
但我现在要和这位小姐说两句
but I do need a word
with the young lady.
所以，提姆，去一边坐下
So, Tim, go sit down,
数到十万
count to 100,000.
小点声，真乖
Quietly now.
There's a good boy.
我猜你知道我是谁
I assume you know who I am.
那我们就废话少说了，好吗？
Then let's get right to it,
shall we?
你现在的困境在我看来
就是交友不慎的绝佳案例啊
Your current dilemma strikes me
as a case of poor alliances.
你忠于马赛尔
You're loyal to Marcel,
而他却把你藏在阁楼里
and yet he keeps you
tucked away in an attic.
你一定更希望多点自由
Surely you'd prefer
just a little bit more freedom,
而马赛尔却把你关起来
and yet Marcel keeps you prisoner.
马赛尔并不是把我关起来
Marcel doesn't keep me prisoner.
他是在保护我
He keeps me safe.
他是我的朋友
He's my friend.
这一点母庸置疑
Well, I have no doubt he is,
但对于一个被卷入
女巫和吸血鬼战争的女孩来说
but for a girl caught in a war
between the witches and the vampires,
我也许可以做个更称职的朋友
I might be a better friend.
我会保护你
I would keep you safe,
同时给你自由
and I'd allow you your freedom.
如果马赛尔能做到这点
If Marcel could do that,
为什么他到现在还不做？
why hasn't he done so already?
而且有个问题你无法回避
And it does beg the question,
如果马赛尔连你都保护不了
if Marcel can't protect you,
那这些你所关心的人又怎么办呢？
then what of those you care about?
如果任何人想要伤害我关心的人
If anyone tries to hurt
anyone I care about,
我会杀了他们
I'll kill them.
好吧
Well, then,
听起来你根本就不需要马赛尔
sounds like you don't need Marcel at all.
也许你早就怀疑了
Perhaps you've suspected it all along.
你的挚友马赛尔骗你
Your dear friend Marcel tricks you
为他做事
into doing his bidding,
一直以来，你独自在阁楼上自生自灭
and all the while,
you rot in an attic alone...
而小提摩西却已开始了新的生活
...while young Timothy
moves on with his life.
你感觉到了吗？
You feel that?
(HlSSlNG, FlzzLlNG)
那是你的血液开始沸腾
That's your blood starting to boil.
真可惜你才与他重聚
Such a shame to lose him
却马上又要失去他
just as you found him again.
我真的很欣赏你的琴艺
And I really did admire
your skill with that violin.
不准伤害他
Don't you dare hurt him!
我也希望不用到那一步，亲爱的
Well, I hope I won't have to, sweetheart,
但这都要看你了
but then that depends on you.
（警戒线 严禁穿越）
马上放开他
Let him go now!
你该知道我最不喜欢人家指使我
You should know
I don't do well with demands.
厉害，但你不会想与我作对的，亲爱的
Impressive,
but you don't want to fight me, love.
无辜的人总是沦为牺牲品
Innocent people have a way
of winding up dead.
求求你放了我
Please let me go.
决定权在你，小女巫
Your choice, little witch.
宣誓只效忠我一人，这男孩就能活下去
Swear allegiance to me alone,
and the boy lives.
如果与我作对…
Stand against me....
不得不说我对你刮目相看了
I have to say I'm impressed.
你怎么找到我的？
How'd you find me?
你的简讯给了我提示
剩下的多亏了吸血鬼听力
Your text got me halfway.
Vamp hearing did the rest.
他们是谁？
Who are they?
女巫，术士，我也不知道
Witches, warlocks,
whatever.
他们还有同伴
There are more of them.
快跑
Run!
我的家人就不能
If I had a dollar for every mess
少给我惹点事吗？
my family's gotten me into.
蕾贝卡
Rebekah!
她在哪？黛维娜在哪？
Where is she?
Where's Davina?
她去圣安妮教堂见一个男孩了
She went to meet a boy
in St. Anne's church.
你在这待着以防她回来
Stay here in case she comes back.
怎么回事？
What the hell?
海莉？
Hayley?
提姆
Tim.
什么叫做她不见了？
What do you mean she's missing?
还能有什么意思？
REBEKAH:
What do you think I mean?
到处都是尸体和血
There's blood and bodies everywhere.
有人在这大开杀戒了
Someone's ripped this lot to shreds,
没看见那个自作聪明的孕妇
and there's no smart-aleck pregnant girl.
继续我，我马上过去
Keep looking.
I'm on my way.
求求你不要伤害我
Please don't hurt me.
我本来也不想这样的
KLAUS:
It wasn't my intent to,
但很遗憾，我没时间装好人了
but sadly,
I've run out of time to play nice.
提姆，不要
Tim?
Oh, no!
不要，求求你
No, please.
我很抱歉，真的很抱歉
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
我不想伤害你的
I didn't mean to hurt you.
战争的悲剧性后果之一
KLAUS: One of the tragic
consequences of war,
就是无辜的旁人受伤
innocent bystanders.
如果小提摩西为你而死
What terrible guilt
you'll have to live with,
你得背负着多大的愧疚过完一生
young Timothy's blood
on your hands.
离他远点
Get away from him!
先别这么急着悲伤
Now, now, let's not be hasty.
毕竟，我可以救他
After all, I can heal him.
只要你…
All you have to do...
求我
...is ask.
求求你
Please.
为了你，黛维娜，乐意之至
For you, Davina, with pleasure.
你不会记得演出后发生的任何事
You will forget everything that
happened after the concert,
包括你和黛维娜见面
including the fact
that you saw Davina.
什么？不
What? No.
如果他记得曾见过你
If he remembers
seeing you,
他可能会四处找你
he might come looking.
如果女巫们知道了他的存在
If the witches learn of him,
她们知道你有弱点
if they know you have a weakness,
可怜的提姆很可能会再一次
then poor Tim might end up
as leverage
当作用来控制你的筹码
in an awful scheme
to control you again.
好了，来，起来吧
Okay. Come on.
Up you come.
带着你的小提琴盒
Take your violin case
with you.
你会记得演出后在后台丢了你的乐器
You'll remember losing the instrument
backstage after the performance.
你真应该更小心点的
You really should be more careful.
搞定了
All fixed.
现在你欠我一个人情
Now, you owe me a favor.
黛维娜
MARCEL: Davina.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
你为什么会在这里？
What are you doing here?
我住在这里，记得吗？
I live her, remember?
你居然放弃追逐权力
Wow, you abandoned
your quest for power
来帮助你的家人
to help out your family.
今天休假吗？
Having an off day?
一谁抓走了她，蕾贝卡？
一我不知道
-Who took her, Rebekah?
-I don't know.
什么叫做你不知道？
What do you mean you don't know?
那是谁杀了攻击她的人？
Then who killed her attackers?
我不知道，我胸口插了根箭
I don't know.
I had an arrow in my heart.
如果不是海莉杀了他们，那么…
If it wasn't Hayley
who killed them, then....
真好，说不定她的亲戚们知道她在哪
Lovely. Perhaps her cousins
will know where she is.
海莉，发生什么事了？快告诉我
Hayley, what happened?
Tell me what happened.
我不记得了
I can't remember.
你的伤口完全愈合了
You've completely healed.
你身上一点伤痕都没有
There's not a scratch on you.
身为狼人的好处之一记得吗？
One of the perks
of being a werewolf, remember?
不，不会好得这么快
No.
Not that fast.
别烦她了
Leave her alone.
是因为这个孩子
It's the baby,
她有吸血鬼的血
克劳斯的血在你身体里
the vampire blood,
Klaus' blood in your system.
可以治愈任何伤口
It can heal any wound.
你的孩子治愈了你
Your own child healed you.
你是怎么逃出来的？
How did you escape?
你寡不敌众还徒手搏斗
You were outnumbered, unarmed.
那些人都被撕成碎片了
Those men were ripped to shreds.
我想是那只狼
I think it was the wolf.
我想他在试图保护我
I think it's trying to protect me.
那些女巫本应保护你的
The witches were
supposed to protect you.
等我抓到苏菲德弗罗…
When I get my hands
on Sophie Deveraux--
那不是苏菲
It wasn't Sophie.
是爱格妮丝
It was Agnes.
好吧，爱格妮丝，苏菲
对我来说都一样
Fine. Agnes, Sophie.
It's all the same to me.
我会把她们杀个片甲不留
I'll slaughter the lot of them.
如果以利亚先到就不行了
Not if Elijah gets there first.
以利亚？
Elijah?
你我到他了？
Did you find him?
一直有联系，而且他有个计划
He's been in touch,
and he has a plan.
他只要求我们照顾好你
All he asked is
that we take care of you.
那么，我们可以回家了吗？
Hey.
So, can we go home now?
我真想好好睡上几天
I'd really like to sleep
for a few days.
哇
Whoa!
接住你了，亲爱的，有我呢
I've got you, love.
I've got you.
我说得非常清楚
I was crystal clear.
随时都要盯着她们俩
Eyes on my girls
at all times.
怎么，那女孩的朋友从你的派对上溜走
Well.... Girl's little friend
sneaks away from your party,
是我们的错吗？
and that's our fault?
怎么，马赛尔，你也要把我关起来吗？
What, Marcel, you gonna send
me to the garden now, too?
他醒来后
When he wakes up,
告诉他这样的态度
tell him that an apology
would have gotten him
还不如直接道歉
a lot further than his attitude.
教堂发生的事真是太糟了
Awful what happened
at the church.
我听说他们声称是瓦斯漏气
I hear they're
calling it a gas leak.
真遗憾
Such a pity.
我听说你今天可是任务繁重
I heard that you were quite
the woman on a mission today.
我能说什么？我想要以利亚回来而已
What can I say?
I want Elijah back.
仅此而已吗？
Is that all you want?
我会还给你以利亚
You'll get Elijah back.
同时，离开酒吧
In the meantime,
stay out of this bar
并且和我手下保持距离
and stay away from my guys.
怎么，你吃醋了？
What's wrong?
You jealous?
我？我已经找到我的女王了
Me? I've already found
my queen.
那个酒保卡蜜吗？
Cami, the bartender?
别欺骗自己了，马赛尔
Stop fooling yourself, Marcel.
她只是你的慰藉食物
She's comfort food.
是让你分心
Something to distract you
不知道自己到底想要什么的慰藉食物
from what you really want.
即使过了这么多年
Which, after all these years,
也不能否认
is impossible to deny
因为你想要的就站在你面前
because I'm standing
right in front of you.
克劳斯？
Klaus?
你怎么来了？
What are you doing here?
已经大半夜了
I've had quite a night.
我想到你说过你做噩梦还失眠
I recall you mentioned something
about nightmares and insomnia.
我想我能帮忙，可以进来吗？
I believe I can help.
May I come in?
这真是太奇怪了
进来吧
This is super weird.
Come in.
等等
Wait.
没错，我告诉过你
That's right.
I told you what happened.
我从没和别人提起过，但却告诉了你
I never tell anybody,
but I told you...
你说过西恩独自一人
...and you said something
about Sean
对抗着心中的恶魔
standing alone against his demons.
当他杀了那些人
When he killed those men,
我想他一定是精神不正常了
I thought he must be mentally ill,
但如果都是因为恶魔呢？
but what if it was demons?
如果是吸血鬼魅惑了他呢？
What if a vampire compelled him?
如果是这样
你会奋不顾身
And if so,
would you devote yourself
去找到罪魁祸首吗？
to finding the guilty party?
你会牺牲一切去找到真相吗？
Would you sacrifice everything
to find out the truth?
到底是为什么？
To what end?
为什么？
这就是我来纽奥良的原因
This is the entire reason
I'm in New Orleans.
卡蜜，这个谜最终的结局
Cami, whatever lies on the
other end of this mystery
只会给你带来痛苦
will only offer you pain.
什么都不能让你哥哥起死回生
Nothing will bring your brother back.
你得到平静的唯一方法就是忘掉这一切
Your only hope for peace
is to forget this.
一不
一并且向前看
-No.
-And move on.
不，别魅惑我忘记这一切
No.
Don't compel me to forget this.
如果我不抹掉你的记忆
And if I allow you to remember,
这一切会侵蚀着你
the knowledge will eat away at you.
你对真相的追寻只会置你于险境
Your quest for truth
will only put you in danger.
你根本不是在关心我
You don't care about me!
你只是想让我忘记
这样我就能把注意集中在马赛尔身上
You just want me to forget this
so I can be focused on Marcel,
我就会乖乖当你的小间谋
so I'll be a good,
little spy for you.
是的，我需要你的忠诚
I need your loyalty, yes,
这对你来说也许很自私
and, though that
may appear selfish to you,
但我的计划远不只是为了我自己
the scope of my plan
goes far beyond myself.
撇开权力，我试图对我哥哥表示尊重
Power aside,
I am trying to honor my brother.
那我哥哥呢？
What about my brother,
我的双胞胎哥哥？
my twin brother?
我们一生都连结在一起
We were bonded our whole lives,
我知道，我知道他不是突然就这样
and I know...
I know he didn't just snap,
我要知道是谁干的
and I need to know who did this,
我希望为他平反
and I need to make this right.
不，不要抹掉我的记忆
No.
Don't take this away from me!
你什么都不会做
You will do nothing.
你哥哥病了
Your bother was ill.
他杀了那些人，然后自杀
He killed those people
and himself,
这是个悲剧
and it was a tragedy.
你能做的就是…
All you can do...
向前看
...is move on.
你知道你哥哥安息了
Know that your brother
is at peace
而且你不用担心
and that you needn't worry.
我会弄清真相
I will find out what happened,
到那时候
and when I do,
不论是谁伤害了你哥哥，我都会让他
I will make sure
whoever harmed your brother...
付出代价
...will suffer.
至于你
And as for you,
今晚，你将入眠
tonight, you will sleep,
梦中的世界要比现实好得多
and you will dream of a world
far better than this one.
一个没有邪恶，没有恶魔的世界
Aworld where there is no evil,
no demons...
那是所有人都在追求的
...and all people desire...
是做一个善良的人
...only to be good.
别担心，黛维娜
It's all right, Davina.
我不会伤害你
I don't mean you any harm.
我想我们是时候谈谈了
Though I do think it's time
we had a talk.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）